远鉴字幕组制作
[Visionary] 0day-sub
翻译&校对：william2568 我问这瓜保熟么
他在那儿
There he is!
超人 能问你几个问题吗
Superman! Superman! Can we ask you some questions?
- 我们要做播客 - 那好吧
- It's for our podcast. - Well, in that case...
你一共救过多少人
How many people that you saved... have you saved?
- 我.. - 算了 下个问题
- I... - Never mind.
那个标记 是代表着希望吗
Does your thing really stand for hope?
对 是的
Yes. It does.
看起来像字母S
But it looks like an "S".
对 这是有内涵的 字母像条蜿蜒的河流
Yes, it's meant to. It's meant to wind, like a river.
河流奔腾不息
It comes and goes.
我的父..
My fa...
我认识的一个人 说过
A man I knew, used to say...
希望就像车钥匙一样
that hope is like a car keys.
容易弄丢 但只要你去找
Easy to lose, but if you dig around...
总能找到的
...it's usually close by.
你跟河马搏斗过吗
Did you ever fight a hippo?
别问这么蠢的问题
That's dumb!
但河马是最危险的动物啊
But hippos are the most deadly!
你最喜欢地球的哪一点
What is... What's the best thing about planet Earth?
新闻标题：超人已死
你干什么
What are you doing?
等等 不要
Wait! No, wait! Wait! Wait!
求你了 老兄 求求你了
Please! Please, man! Please!
你想要我怎样
What do you want from me?
恐惧
Fear.
它们能闻到恐惧
They could smell it.
Janus：杰纳斯化妆品公司 大反派“黑面具”[未出现]的家族产业
什么情况
What the hell?
- 那是什么 - 一个侦察兵
- What was that? - A scout.
从太空来的? 外星大军要入侵了?
From space? Like an alien army?
阿尔弗雷德 你看到了这些么
Alfred, are you seeing this?
看到了 和其它的目击事件情况一致
I am. Matches the other sightings.
卢瑟的笔记里全都是那种图案
And that pattern is all over Luthor's notes.
准备飞机 我们今晚去北方
Prep the jet. I'm going north tonight.
好 是时候了
Good. It's time, then.
这是因为他们知道他死了 对吧
It's 'cause they know he's dead, right?
我是说超人 他死了
Superman. He's gone.
我们以后要指望谁呢
Where does that leave us?
超人左边是英国摇滚神祗大卫·鲍伊 右边美国流行乐传奇人物普林斯 和大超一样 均死于2016年
新闻标题：他们回到自己的母星了吗
放下武器
Drop your guns now!
抱歉 你..
Excuse me?
- 让开 - 别开枪
- Move it. Move! - Don't shoot!
都趴下
Get down.
让他们都靠墙蹲下 让他们闭嘴
Line them up along the wall. Keep them quiet.
雕像：希腊神话中的“正义女神”忒弥斯 原型位于伦敦老巴里街英格兰和威尔士刑事法庭的顶端
你们是什么人
Who are you?
用真言套索套住你了 你说出来的都是真话
The lasso of Hestia compels you to reveal the truth.
给我从实招来
Now, who are you?
我们是一个小型的恐怖组织
We're a small group of reactionary terrorists.
我们知道地球的罪恶
We know that sinners brought
- 招致了外星入侵 - 为什么抓人质
- on this plague of... - Why the hostages?
你来晚了 倒计时已经开始
You're too late. The countdown's already begun.
几分钟后 这四个街区 将在全世界的注视下
In a few minutes, 4 city blocks...
灰飞烟灭
While the world watches.
安静 闭嘴
Shut up!
这是人类最后的希望
This is man's best hope.
毁灭现代世界
Down with the modern world.
回到黑暗时代
Back to the Dark Ages.
才能得到神的庇护
And the safety of holy fear.
本来早就了结了 但是..
This would've been over quickly, but...
不 不要
No! Don't!
怎么可能
I don't believe it.
爱的信徒：在《神奇女侠》电影中，神奇女侠表示自己相信爱的力量
- 来者何人  - 一个爱的信徒而已
- What are you? - A believer.
请各位帮我一个忙
I'm asking for your help.
我知道有个陌生人 从海里来到了这个村庄
I believe there's a stranger, comes to this village from the sea.
每年冬天的时候 人们没吃的 他来到这里
He comes in the winter when the people are hungry...
带来很多鱼
and brings fish.
他来的时候 潮水非常高
He comes on the king tide...
也就是说 他昨晚来的
That was last night.
港口有冰山
Icebergs in the harbour.
四个月没有船进来了
Four months since the last ship got through.
这个陌生人
Well, this stranger...
不是坐船来的
Doesn't come by ship.
有敌人要来了 从很远的地方来
There are enemies coming, from far away.
我需要战士
I need warriors.
我在组建一个联盟 保卫我们的家园
I'm building an alliance, to defend ourselves.
听着 让我马上跟他去外面谈会话
Look, I'll give you $25,000 to...
我就给你
talk to this man right now...
两万五千美金
outside.
我觉着不管我告不告诉他 这钱最后他都得给我的
Something tells me that of all he will give them to me.
告诉我这三个盒子是什么东西 我给你三万
Tell me what those 3 boxes are and I'll make it 30.
你应该滚出去
You should get out.
你至少应该明着告诉我去亚特兰蒂斯吧
Can you at least point me to Atlantis?
亚瑟·库里
Arthur Curry.
海的保护者
Also known as the Protector of the Oceans.
你是海王
The Aquaman.
我听说你能跟鱼说话
I hear you can talk to fish.
跟鱼说话：《超人：钢铁之躯》中 超人在钻井平台大爆炸后坠入海中 被几条鲸鱼所救 就是海王控制的
我得把话说清楚
So let me get this straight...
你扮成蝙蝠的样子 就像真的蝙蝠那样?
You do it dressed like a bat? Like an actual bat?
二十年来 哥谭市的人们都信以为真呢
It's worked for 20 years in Gotham.
就那个破地方
Oh, that shithole.
开战的时候 我们需要你
The fight comes, we'll need you.
- 别指望我去凑热闹 - 为什么
- Don't count on it, Batman. - Why not?
因为 我不喜欢你来这里
Because I don't like you coming here...
问东问西 打搅我的生活
digging into my business, getting into my life.
亚特兰蒂斯的人对我指手画脚
People from Atlantis tell me, "Do this."
现在你又找上门了
Now, you say, "Do that."
我想清静点
I want to be left alone.
所以你就躲在这个荒凉的地方帮助渔民
That why you help these people out here in the middle of nowhere?
因为在这你可以消极避世?
Because you can just leave?
我帮助他们 是因为没人对他们伸出援手
I help them 'cause no one else does.
想保护他们 你得跟我合作
You wanna protect them, you need to work with me.
单枪匹马的英雄才是最强的
A strong man is strongest alone.
听过这句话没
You ever heard that?
那句话不是这么说的 你正好说反了
That's not a saying. That's the opposite of what the saying is.
那行 这并不代表我说的就是错的
Yep. Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
你听说过超人吗
You ever hear of Superman?
他与我并肩作战时去世了 - 我没说反吧
- He died fighting next to me. - My point exactly.
那三个盒子里是什么
What's in the 3 boxes?
它们的起源很古老了
It's ancient history.
人类活动使得极地的冰盖融化
Mankind's melting the polar ice caps...
破坏了生态系统 所以报应来了?
Destroying the ecosystem, they got it coming?
我又不介意海面升高
Hey, I don't mind if the ocean rise.
如果海水沸腾了呢
How about if they boil?
装扮成蝙蝠的模样
Dressed like a bat.
你疯了 布鲁斯·韦恩
You're out of your mind, Bruce Wayne.
这并不代表我说的就是错的
Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
所以 你是说 你没法再联系上这个所谓的
So, you say you have no way of reconnecting with this...
海王了
Aquaman.
我在他外套里放了跟踪器
I put a tracking device in his coat...
可他脱掉外套游走了
He left without it.
实际上 那可能根本不是他的外套
It may, in fact, not have been his coat.
卢瑟的笔记中 画的那些盒子
Those squares, from Luthor's notes...
会不会是某种容器呢
I think they must be containers of some kind.
- 装什么的呢 - 不知道
- Of what? - I don't know.
也许可以带来金钱 权力 总之值得为它们发动一场战争
Money, power. Something worth starting a war over.
幸好我找到了
Well, we had luck with one person...
名单里的一个人
on the team list.
巴里·艾伦 住在中心城
Barry Allen, of Central City.
他基本上是与世隔绝
He's completely off the grid.
估计靠占用闲置的房屋为生
Squatting, I think.
经常突然搬家
Moves suddenly and often.
- 可能是那种喜欢玩失踪的人? - 但他会定期探望父亲
- Disappearing act? - But he does visit his father...
他父亲
...in prison.
- 因为谋杀了他的母亲进了监狱 - 我的天
- For murdering his mother. - Jesus!
巴里小时候总说他父亲被冤枉了
Young Barry always protested his father's innocence...
可他那时才九岁 没人理会他
But he was 9 and nobody listened to him.
监狱那边有认识的人么
We have somebody at the prison?
有的 我们会搞到监狱地址的
Oh, yeah. We'll find the address.
- 有没有联系戴安娜 - 你有她的电话号码
- What about, Diana? - Well, you have her number.
你打电话给她就行了
You could've called her.
要不要我带上你的亲笔信
Perhaps I should fly to Paris
立刻飞到巴黎找她
with a handwritten note?
上面写着"你愿意当布鲁斯的队友吗"
"Will you be Bruce' teammate?"
"请选是或否"
"Check: Yes or No"
我只对她的技能感兴趣
I'm only interested in her skill set.
- 那当然了 - 回归正题吧
- I'm sure you are. - Can we?
这次的面部识别情况有点复杂
Well, facial recognition's a bit dodgy on this one.
不过已经有部分吻合的结果了
But it's got a partial match.
这个人叫维克多·斯通
A Victor Stone.
智商超群 拿过橄榄球奖学金
Genius I.Q., football scholarship to GCU...
而且 他已经去世了
And deceased.
太好了 全是神神鬼鬼的事情
Figures. Fairy tales and ghost stories.
真怀念以前的日子 当时最大的麻烦
One misses the days when one's biggest
不过是会爆炸的发条企鹅而已
concerns were exploding wind-up penguins?
企鹅人：1992年电影《蝙蝠侠归来》中的反派
日子多简单啊
The simple life.
我已经看不转这个世界了
I don't recognize this world.
我不需要看透这个世界
I don't have to recognize it.
我只需要拯救世界
I just have to save it.
我来探望亨利·艾伦
Here to see Henry Allen.
签字
Sign.
动作快点 小子
Hurry it up, will you?
怎么 你想打架么
What, you got a problem?
没事 我不想打架
No. There's no problem.
算你识相
Better not be.
你知道该去哪的
You know where to go.
你这是出门忘吃药了...
Are those prescription...
还是想秀智商?
Or you just trying to look brainy?
因为你自己困住了自己 你在原地打转
Because you're holding yourself back. You're going in circles.
做着三份没前途的工作 还准备找第四份
You're working 3 dead- end jobs. Going on four.
你哪来这么多时间
Where do you even have the time?
我会挤时间做的
I make the time.
这都是为了挣修读刑事司法学位的学费 对吧
And this is all to pay for a criminal justice degree, huh?
巴里·艾伦父亲：由比利·克鲁德普扮演 也曾在扎导的电影《守望者》中扮演曼哈顿博士
好了 我真的不想再谈这个了
Okay. I really don't want to talk about this again...
他们的调查漏洞百出
The investigation was botched.
伸出你的手 巴里
Give me your hand.
认真听我说 巴里
I want you to listen to me, Barry...
我是认真的
Because I mean this.
你不要再坚持了
I want you to give all of that up.
也不要再来这儿探望我
And I want you to stop coming to see me.
我拖累了你的人生
I am a drag on your life.
别再跟我说这样的话了
Please don't ever say that to me again.
好吗
Please?
你能心想事成的 你是个聪明的孩子
You can be whatever you wanna be. You're a brilliant man.
精英中的精英
Absolute best of the best.
我不忍心坐在这里
I can't sit here...
看着你为了我这个老头子
and watch you run in place in Central City...
在中心城原地踏步
for some old dude...
- 我已经困在这里了 - 爸爸
- who's not going anywhere. - Dad...
- 别这么说 - 时间到了
- That's not true. - It's time.
- 别这么说 - 走吧 艾伦
- That's not true. - Let's go, Allen.
艾伦
Allen!
你要把握好你的未来 艾伦
I want you to make your own future.
不要活在过去 把握好未来
Living in the past... Make your own future.
开门
Open gate!
你可以进实验室打扫了 霍华德
Lab's all yours, Howard.
十一点半 今天回家挺早啊 赛拉斯
11:30. Early night for you, Silas.
是的 挺早的
Yes. Early.
一直没机会跟您说
I never got to say...
你儿子的遭遇 真是令人遗憾
I'm very sorry about what happened.
维克多是个好孩子
Victor was a wonderful kid.
谢谢
Thank you.
维克多
Victor.
维克多 你不要止步不前
Victor, you're not stuck up here.
你可以有自己的生活 而不是...
You can have a life. You can have more than...
- 如果你一直在这里胡思乱想 - 我在处理数据
- If you stay up here brooding... - I'm processing.
我能访问一切数据
I can access everything.
- 但我没法把它们组合在一起 - 先别急
- But I can't put it all together. - Not yet.
如果你要让我帮忙 如果有再造引擎
But if you work with me, if we had the change engines...
那你还是会把其他人 变成我这样
So you did to someone else. What you did to me.
不 要把盒子藏好
No. The box stays hidden.
我们从氪星飞船上学到了很多东西
If you could see what we're learning from the Kryptonian ship...
我认为再造引擎可以整合它的能量
I think the change engine can integrate with its energy...
- 给它充能 然后.. - 有人知道么
- get it powered up... - Does anybody know?
知道什么
What?
实验室那边 有人知道我还活着吗
At the lab... Does anybody know I'm alive?
我...我..
I... I...
我觉得他们还没准备好...
I didn't think you were ready for them to...
准备什么?
For what?
还没准备好看到我变成了怪物么
For them to see the monster?
你不是怪物
You are not a monster.
你竟然觉得我说的是我自己 真奇怪啊
It's weird that you thought I meant me.
我...
What I did...
那场事故夺走了你的母亲的生命
I lost your mother in that accident.
我不能再..
I wasn't about to...
我不能再失去我的儿子
I couldn't bear to lose my son.
但你已经失去了
But you did.
现在我脑子里有种我不会说的语言
I got a language in my head that I don't speak.
不止是数据流那么简单 而是一种外星的产物
It's not just digital... It's alien.
每天我醒来的时候 都感觉不一样
Everyday, I wake up, different...
觉得自己在进化
Modified.
什么意思
How do you...?
我昨晚的时候 还不会这招呢
Couldn't do that last night.
自从氪星人来到地球
Ever since we got visitors from Krypton,
人们就在等待下一次外星人入侵
people have been waiting for the next alien invasion.
现在我就想 我自己可能就是个外星人
Now I got to wonder if I'm it?
- 今天有变化么 - 没有 陛下
- Any changes today? - No, my Queen.
母盒已经苏醒
The Mother Box has awoken...
但目前相安无事
Yet, nothing has happened.
从第一纪元起 母盒已经沉睡了数千年
It has slept for thousands of years, since the first age.
它为何苏醒了呢
Why did it wake at all?
亚马逊族 准备战斗
Amazons, on your mark!
荒原狼
Steppenwolf.
母亲
Mother...
我流浪了数千年 一直在寻找您
Millenia in exile... Searching.
您终于召我回家了
At last, you call me home.
你不会喜欢这个欢迎仪式的
You will not like your welcome.
我觉得会的呢
Oh, I think I will.
- 集合部队 - 封锁这里
- Gather the legions. - Seal the cage!
快去
Go!
从右边夹击
Flank right!
很好
Yes...
跑啊
Run.
封住大门
Seal the gates!
把它带的越远越好
Keep it moving.
拿到了 快走
Got it! Go!
高贵的女王 你为何反抗
Noble Queen, why do you fight?
三个母盒统一之后后 你会加入我的军团的
After the Unity, you will join my Legion...
你会明白权力就是正义
and you will know the righteousness of power.
你会爱上我的：DC大反派达克赛德的反生命方程 能操控一切的生灵的意念 进而可以奴役人类统治地球
你会爱上我的
You will love me.
你们都会的
You all will.
我们要点燃远古烽火
We have to light the ancient warning fire.
烽火已经有五千年没有点燃了
The fire has not burned for 5,000 years.
人类不明白它的含义
Men won't know what it means.
人类确实不明白
Men won't...
但她明白
But she will.
看好了 戴安娜
Listen to me, Diana.
上周末你做什么去了 戴安娜
What did you do this weekend, Diana?
我么
Me?
做了些无聊的事
Nothing very interesting.
你每次都这么说
That's all you ever tell us.
我能怎么说 我是个无趣的人
Whay can I say? I'm not that exciting.
亚马逊族神殿
...Shrine of the Amazons...
好大一团火堆燃烧着 就在我身后
an enormous bonfire burned right behind me...
当地居民和政府部门
baffling absolutely everyone...
全部惊呆了
from locals, to government authorities alike.
- 数英里之外都能看到火光 - 有敌人入侵了
- The fire could be seen for miles on end... - Invasion.
下面播报本地新闻
On the local scene...
这位是看门人的妻子
This janitor's wife had some strong words...
对外星人一顿臭骂 她自称外星人
for the aliens she says,
勾引走了她的丈夫
stole her man.
我老公是个好人 他是养家的人
My Howard is a good man. He's a provider.
这些外星人真的要(哔)他?
And these aliens are gonna (beep) probe him?
有种来湖景公寓
Come down to the Lakeview...
信不信我弄死你们这些外星混账
And I'll stick a (beep) probe up your alien (beep) ass, you...
我找到了一处地方 在餐馆附近
I found a little place. By the diner.
挺适合我的
Suits me just fine.
你应该把这事告诉我啊
I wish you'd said something.
没事 我没按期还款
Oh, no. I got behind in the payments.
你也知道 少交一毛钱 银行立马就翻脸
And you know the banks. Jump like a cougar if you miss by a dime.
房子我一个人住太大了
Place was too big for me anyway.
住在里面我瘆得慌
Shuffling around like an old ghost.
你早些告诉我的话 我可以找人帮你 或者
Well, I might have been able to, talk to someone, or...
你已经够忙了
You had enough to deal with.
就别为婆婆操心了
Don't need to add mother-in-law to the list.
- 虽然不是正式的.. - 嘿 露易丝
- Not that I was ever... - Hey, Lane...
你的线人是谁 是不是那个大学的一个活跃分子...
Who is your source? The activist in that university...
是的 那是我的线人
Look, it's my source.
他们要我写那个绑架案
I got tapped for the kidnapping story.
那些学生都在抗议
There were all those student protests. Anyway...
我觉得是跟政治有关 能告诉我他的真实身份么
I'm thinking it's political, so... Who's your guy?
我帮你问问那姑娘愿不愿意和你接触
Well let's see if she'll take your call.
原来是个女的
So, it's a she.
其实不是女的
It's not a she.
感觉你应该去写那个新闻了
Sounds like you should be working that story.
我还没准备好呢
I'm... I'm not ready yet.
我是很乐意写点宠物美容妙招什么的
I'm perfectly happy, doing fluff pieces about kitten grooming.
调节一下
For a while...
回来之后 心情挺沉重的
It was hard coming back here at all.
我连新闻都不敢多看
Well. I can hardly read the news anyway.
越看越难过
So much bitterness.
当然 这都是因为他不在了
'Course, I think it's all because he's gone.
可能母亲都这样
But I suppose a mother does.
不过 值得报道的事情还挺多的
But it's not like there's any less that needs reporting.
克拉克说过 你肯定会再拿一个普利策奖的
And Clark promised me, you were gonna bring home another Pulitzer.
- 是吗 - 当然 他说过
- Oh, did he? - Oh, yes. He did.
他说你是他见过最饥渴的女人
He said you were the thirstiest young woman he'd ever met.
- 不是饥渴 是机智 - 机智 嗯..
- Hungriest. - Hungry. Yeah.
他说你的新闻嗅觉
He said you...
是比他灵敏的多
could smell a story. Further away than he could hear.
那些故事互相有联系
Well stories, made sense.
我不仅仅要解谜 我还要揭示真相
It was more than just a puzzle. It was about the truth.
就像 你要趁驱动世界的引擎还在运转的时候
It was about seeing the engine of the world...
去发现它
While it still ran.
维克多·斯通
Victor Stone...
已经去世了
Deceased.
就是那个
That one...
我敢肯定 就是这种声音让外星人很难受
Pretty sure that's what made the alien go crazy.
我来想办法把这个整合到你的装备上
I'll see about weaving something to the suit.
需要点时间了
Won't be quick.
只要能派上用场就行
Anything to give me an edge.
你知道的 我在这栋楼的安保系统上
You know, I paid millions of dollars...
花了几百万
for this building's security.
对 看起来挺贵的
Yeah. It looked expensive.
嗨
Hi.
这是你的新玩具吗
A new toy?
军队运输机 原型机
Prototype troop carrier.
这个家伙指《神奇女侠》中出现的空军上校史蒂夫·特雷弗
我以前认识个家伙 他喜欢开这玩意
I once knew a man who would've loved to fly it.
对 光是飞行员还不够
Yeah, well we're gonna need more than a pilot.
我觉得敌人要来了
I think there's an attack coming.
不是要来 布鲁斯 已经来了
Not coming, Bruce. It's already here.
人们称其 荒原狼
They called him Steppenwolf.
世界的终结者
The End of Worlds.
他生来就是为了征服
He lived only to conquer.
数百万死在他斧下的人
Millions fell before his blade...
会复活 变成类魔
And rose again as his Parademons.
一种以恐惧为食的恐怖生物
Nightmare creatures, who feed on fear.
对 碰到过一只 相处不是很愉快
Yeah, I think I've met one. We didn't hit it off.
在哥谭市遇到的么
Here in Gotham?
到处都能见着它们
They're all over.
在寻找他的盒子吗
They're looking for his... Boxes?
- 母盒 - 母盒？
- The Mother Boxes. - Mother Boxes?
我猜荒原狼抢走了你们族人守护的那个
I guess Steppenwolf sent the winged people
还剩两个
that leaves two more.
- 你挺厉害啊 - 过奖了
- I'm impressed. - Don't be.
我还不知道里面是什么
I have no idea what's in them.
武器 还是某种力量
A weapon? Some kind of power?
盒子里没有力量
They don't contain power.
盒子本身就是力量
They are power.
它们把母盒从一个星球搬到另一个上去
Carried from planet to planet...
合并之后会形成统一之力
The Mother Boxes combined to form the Unity.
那种强大的能量不仅可以毁灭星球
An apocalyptic power that not only destroys worlds...
还能把星球变成满目疮痍的空壳
...but transforms them into the primordial hell's gate...
就像荒原狼的家乡那样
...of Steppenwolf's birthworld.
眼看地球要沦陷
We should have died...
但地球的统一之力迸发出来
But we formed our own Unity.
亚马逊族 亚特兰蒂斯族
Amazons, Atlanteans...
人类各族并肩作战
All the tribes of man fought side by side.
传奇战士
Warriors of legend.
龙型绿灯侠：亚兰·戈
来自异域空间的盟友
Allies from other worlds.
甚至众神也齐心协力
Even the gods themselves all acted as one.
不惜献出生命将荒原狼击退
Laying down their lives to drive Steppenwolf away.
绿灯戒：每一个绿灯侠都有一个绿灯戒 能产生各式各样的效果 靠配戴者的想像力与意志力强度来维持
操纵闪电的是宙斯
战神阿瑞斯 《神奇女侠》中也出现过
狩猎女神阿尔忒弥斯
据说荒原狼恼羞成怒
Some say it drove him mad...
因为他从未吃过败仗
.. the disgrace of his first retreat.
他发誓要击溃我们的联盟
He swore our alliance would crumble.
黑暗将笼罩地球
That darkness would cover the Earth...
到时候他就会再回来
And that he would return when it did.
他留下的
Left behind...
母盒太过危险
The Mother Boxes were too dangerous
决不能放在一处
to be kept together.
于是把其中一个托付给亚马逊族
One was entrusted to the Amazons.
一个托付给亚特兰蒂斯族
One, to the Atlanteans.
两个都放在戒备森严的堡垒中
Both sealed and guarded in secure strongholds.
把人类之盒埋在秘密之处
The Box of Man was buried in secret.
这样的话 任何族群都无法用它的力量相互攻击
So that no tribe would be tempted to use its power over another.
共度浩劫 重塑和平
Such harmony out of such horror.
那时代真是英雄辈出
It was truly an age of heroes.
我觉得当年的英雄恐怕再难聚首了
Something tells me we're not getting the band back together.
亚特兰蒂斯族被迫潜入海底
The Atlanteans were a force under sea...
亚马逊族藏在海岛不能离开
And the Amazons, to an island they can never leave.
我对人类各族不抱期望
I wouldn't count on the tribes of men.
末日时钟：由芝加哥大学的《原子科学家公报》杂志于1947年设立 标示出世界受核武威胁的程度 时钟上的午夜零时象征核战爆发
大难临头了我们还不愿意面对
We tend to act like the doomsday clock has a snooze button.
- 我们还剩多久  - 几天
- How long until we... - Days.
没几天了
At most.
荒原狼上次胆敢攻击我们就是错误的
Steppenwolf's mistake last time was attacking us.
他想在毁灭地球之前让人类臣服
He wanted to make the Earth kneel before he destroyed us.
这次他只是想夺取母盒而已
This time he'll just go after the Boxes.
我刚刚收到了一个队友的位置
I got a location for one of our recruits.
- 叫巴里·艾伦 - 另一个找到了吗
- Barry Allen. - What about the other one?
维克多·斯通
Victor Stone?
我还希望你能把他找出来呢
I was hoping you would dig him up.
我们这是让他们去冒生命危险 而我们都跟他们不熟
We're asking people we don't know to risk their lives.
我知道
I know.
但也没办法了
That's how this works.
右边显示屏播放的是动画神剧《瑞克和莫蒂》S01E09
后方显示屏：韩国女团BLACKPINK大热单曲《As if It’s your last》的MV
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen.
我是布鲁斯·韦恩
Bruce Wayne.
你以为打声招呼 就能解释清楚
You say that like it explains...
你这样一个陌生人为何闯进我家
why there's a total stranger in my place...
灯也不开 坐在我第二喜欢的椅子上?
sitting in the dark, in my second favorite chair.
来给我解释一下吧
Tell me about this.
这个人跟我长得一模一样
This is a person who looks exactly like me...
但绝对不是我
but who is definitely not me.
这是个非常帅气的犹太小伙啊
Very attractive Jewish boy.
我猜猜看 他是不是偷了你的怀表
Somebody who, I don't know, stole your pocketwatch?
还是铁路?
Or railroads?
我知道你有特殊能力 只是不清楚具体是什么
I know you have abilities. I just don't know what they are.
我的特殊能力有这些
My special skills include...
中提琴 网页设计 能用手语流畅交流
Viola, web design, fluent in sign language...
指闪电侠的对手大猩猩格鲁德 在美剧《闪电侠》中出现过
大猩猩手语
gorilla sign language...
这材质是 硅质石英纤维
Silica-based quartz sand fabric,
抗磨损 抗热
Abrasion resistant. Heat resistant.
没错 这是
Yeah, I do...
- 这是我花样滑冰时用的 - 他们把这个用在
- Competitive ice dancing. - That's what they use...
航天飞机上
on the space shuttle, to
这是飞机返回大气层所需的阻燃材料
prevent it from burning up on re-entry.
我花样滑冰时 动作非常剧烈
I do very competitive ice dancing.
不管你想找谁 绝对不是我
Whoever you're looking for, it's not me...
你是蝙蝠侠
You're the Batman?
这么看来 你动作很快啊
So you're fast.
你的措辞似乎太笼统了点
That feels like an oversimplification.
我在组建一个团队
I'm putting together a team.
需要有特殊能力的人
People with special abilities.
因为我觉得敌人就要来了
You see, I believe enemies are coming.
别说了 我加入
Stop right there. I'm in.
真的
You are?
对 我需要同类
Yeah. I need... friends.
普通人太难相处 我没有那个耐心
People are difficult. They require a lot of focus.
他们的节奏我实在是没法理解
They have like a rhythm that I haven't quite been able to...
你看 早午餐
Like, Brunch?
比如 早午餐是个什么玩意
Like... What is Brunch?
排队等一个小时后
You wait in line for an hour...
拿到的明明就是午餐
for, essentially, lunch.
怎么说呢
I mean, I don't know.
他们太慢了
People are... a little slow.
我尽量跟上你的节奏
I'll try to keep up.
这个能送给我吗
Can I keep this?
我可以进入另一层维度
It's like this layer of dimensional reality...
在那里似乎能够操纵时空
that seems to manipulate space-time.
我称之为神速力
I call it the Speed Force.
使用神速力会让我消耗巨量的卡路里
Causes me to burn tremendous amount of calories...
所以我简直就是个黑洞 要吃大量的零食
So I am just a black hole of snacks.
我是个零食洞
I am a "snack hole."
这个特战小队 现在有多少人
How many people are on this special fight team?
三个 包括你
Three. Including you.
才三个 敌人是谁
Three? Against what?
上了飞机再告诉你
I'll tell you on the plane.
坐飞机啊
Plane?
你的超能力是什么
What are your superpowers again?
我有钱
I'm rich.
每次播放这段录像 电脑就出毛病
The program always gets twitchy with this footage.
戴安娜·普林斯 布鲁斯·韦恩为何找我
Why are you and Bruce Wayne looking for me?
你知道我们是谁?
You know who we are?
我还知道你们的另一重身份
And I also know where you are.
你是维克多·斯通
Are you Victor Stone?
曾是
Was.
我要和你谈谈
I need to speak to you.
谈吧
You are.
不是 面对面的
No, face to face.
我喜欢传统的方式
I'm old-fashioned that way.
我为何要信任你
Why would I trust you?
如果我打算伤害你 我在湖边早动手了
If I was going to attack you, I would've done it by the lake.
看来你要去跟他碰头了 普林斯小姐
Looks like you have a date, Ms. Prince.
是时候派一位英雄去见他了
About time somebody here did.
面对面嘛
Face to face.
我一直在追踪它
I've been doing some tracking.
你要找的东西在无信号区里面
What you're looking for is sticking to the dead zones.
待它现身 能量值激增
It gets in front of a camera, causes a surge.
- 我会通知你的 - 这还不够
- I'll let you know. - That's not good enough.
还不够么
Not good enough?
对你来说 还不够
For you.
我不认识你
Look, I don't know you...
我也不知道你哪来的这些天赋
And I don't know how you got these gifts.
天赋
Gifts?
没人拥有你身上的这些能力
No one else can do what you do.
如果这些能力是天赐的
No, if these are gifts...
那为什么我还要为之付出代价
then why am I the one paying for them?
我们需要你 维克多
We need you, Victor.
也许 你也会需要我们的
And maybe you need us.
我一个人挺好
I'll be fine alone.
很久以前我也是这么想的
I told myself the same for a long time.
我失去了我深爱的人
I lost someone I loved once.
把自己封闭起来 谁也不见
I shut myself off from... From everyone.
我得试着重新敞开心扉
But I had to learn to open back up again.
说实话 我现在还在尽力
The truth is I'm still working on it.
我相信 你这次同意见我
And if you agreed to meet me...
也是在努力多与他人接触
...you're working on it, too.
相信我 维克多
Trust me, Victor.
救命
Mayday! Mayday!
有东西从天上掉下来了
Something came down from the sky.
快救救我
Please, help me!
威士忌
Whisky.
给他也来一杯
And one for Ahab there.
在天上
...from the sky...
我听到一声炮响
I heard a cannon.
- 他这是吓傻了 - 他们来了
- It's ocean's rage. - Then they came...
从天上
Monsters.
来的怪物
...from the sky.
砸穿了我的船
Tore right through my boat.
怪物
Monsters...
他来买单
It's on him.
你撞得不轻啊
You took a hell of a hit.
还好吧
You all right?
终于回来了
At last...
亚特兰蒂斯女王的长子
The firstborn of beloved Queen Atlanna.
等等
Wait.
别走
Please.
我认识女王
I knew her.
你认识她 我可不认识
That makes one of us.
我父母战死了之后
When my parents fought in the wars...
- 她收养了我 - 多么高尚啊
- She took me in. - What a saint.
你胆敢用这种语气提起亚特兰蒂斯女王?
You dare speak of Queen Atlanna that way?
你的女王把我扔在了我父亲的家门口
Your Queen left me on my father's doorstep
头也不回的就走了
and never gave me another thought...
你妈妈离开是为了救你
Your mother left you to save your life.
你不知道她有多伤心
You can't imagine how it hurt her.
她付出了多大的代价
What it cost her.
但你现在已经长大成人了
But you're not a defenseless child now.
追上怪物 阻止他作恶
It would've been her responsibility...
这是女王的职责
to follow that monster to the surface and stop it.
现在 是你的了
Now, it's yours.
那你得给我件东西
Then I'm gonna need something from you.
别弄了
Leave that.
它已经坏了
Leave it. It will never work.
明白了 母亲
I see, Mother.
我明白你为何等到现在才召唤我
I see why you waited to summon me.
氪星人之死让这个胆怯的世界
That Kryptonian's death plunged this timid world...
陷入恐惧
into such terror.
亚马逊族 亚特兰蒂斯族 已被逐一击败
Amazons. Atlanteans. Each stands, and falls, alone.
放心 母亲 这一刻 你等待了太久
I know Mother. You've waited too long for the Unity.
吞噬他们的恐惧吧
I know. But you will feed.
我的流亡生活到此为止
And my exile will come to an end.
新神：漫画中“新神族”是宇宙中最强大的种族 强大的母盒正是新神族的产物
我要成为新神
I will take my place among the New Gods.
找到最后一个母盒
Find the last one.
它的力量将会净化这个世界
Its power will cleanse this world.
为了统一之力
For the Unity!
达克赛德：DC最强反派之一 天启星的统治者 拥有欧米伽效应的力量
为了黑暗君主达克赛德
For Darkseid.
维克多
Victor.
混蛋
Asshole!
八起绑架案 六起在大都会 两起在这里
Eight kidnappings. 6 in Metropolis, 2 here.
遭到绑架的均为星际实验室的工作人员
All the vics worked for STAR Labs.
袭击者是只会飞的吸血鬼
Attacked by a flying vampire.
是一只长着大獠牙的
Suspect was a giant bat...
巨型蝙蝠
with huge fangs.
其中一个目击者是个孩子 吓坏了
One of them was a little kid, scared.
说不出话 但画了这个
Won't say a word but drew this.
- 看起来像 - 我知道你的意思
- Looks like... - I know what it looks like.
拜托 他在这里打击罪犯二十年了
Come on. You think he fights criminals for 20 years here...
你觉得他会去大都会绑架八个人？
and then he goes to Metropolis and kidnaps eight people?
我今晚找他谈谈
I'll talk to him tonight.
这世界已经疯了 局长 也许他也疯了
The world's gone crazy, Jim. Maybe he did, too.
找到钢骨了吗
You find the Cyborg?
和他谈过了
We spoke.
给他点时间
Give him time.
你就是巴里啊 我是戴安娜
You must be Barry. I'm Diana.
巴里 我是戴安娜
Hi Barry, I'm Diana...
说反了 抱歉
That's not right. Great.
所以就我们几个
So this is us?
对 就我们几个
Yeah. This is us.
厉害
Oh! Awesome!
ACE广告牌：ACE化学工厂 《自杀小队》中小丑女和小丑在这里跳入了化学制剂池
那个蝙蝠图案 那是你的
That's the Bat-signal. That's your...
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
有人发信号找你 我们该走了
That's your signal. That means we have to go now.
- 对 是的 就是这样的 - 真是太酷了
- Yeah. That's what that means. - That's so cool.
你这样的蝙蝠侠 有几个?
How many of you are there?
没几个
Not enough.
星际实验室的八名工作人员被绑架
Eight people abducted from or near STAR Labs.
嫌犯长这样
Here's the potential perp.
这是类魔
Parademons.
好吧
Okay...
类魔肯定是闻到了母盒发出的味道
The demons must have caught the scent of a Mother Box.
它们把人绑走 审问他们
They carried people away to find out what they know.
- 那八个人可能还活着 - 现在是九个了
- So the eight might still be alive. - Nine.
星际实验室的主管也遭到绑架
The head of STAR Labs was taken as well.
你来了
You made it.
那么 附近肯定有个类魔巢穴
So then. There must be a nest nearby.
我分析了大都会和哥谭市的各个目击地点
I plotted all the sightings in Metropolis, Gotham...
没看出什么花样
No pattern I can see.
地图上的连线并不交汇
The lines on the map don't converge.
在陆地上
On land.
这些线指向布里克斯顿岛 位于两座城市之间
These lead back to Braxton Island, between the two cities.
哥谭港 那是排气管
Gotham Harbor. These are air vents...
它们均通向大都会的地下隧道网络
they all lead down to the tunnel from Metropolis...
其兴建计划于1929年搁置了
project that was abandoned in '29.
你们真的认为..
Do you really think that...
哇 他们就..他们就这么凭空消失了
Wow. They just... They really just vanished.
真没礼貌
That's rude.
- 我们现在到哪儿了 阿尔弗雷德 - 布拉克斯顿岛
- Where are we, Alfred? - Braxton Island.
你们应该
You should be...
就在隧道通风塔的正下方
directly under the venting tower for the tunnel.
往左看应该有一段楼梯
Now, look to your left, you should see a staircase.
爬上去应该可以直接进入机房
It will give you access to the machine room.
真是够直接啊
Define access.
我们一个一个过
One at a time.
桥可能承受
The bridge may not...
不住
...hold.
- 给我说实话就行 - 求你了 放我们走吧
- Just tell me the truth. - Please, just let us go.
- 我还有家人 - 回答错误
- I have a family! - Wrong answer.
人类
Humans...
你们恐惧的气味让我的士兵垂涎欲滴
The stench of your fear is making my soldiers hungry.
我是不是应该把你们喂给我的手下
Shall I feed them?
你靠近过母盒
You've been near the Mother Box.
- 你身上有它的气味 - 饶命
- The scent is on you... - Please.
我们还有家人
We have families.
为什么每个人都这么说
Why does everyone keep telling me that?
是这样的
Okay. Here's the thing...
我害怕虫子
See, I'm afraid of bugs, and...
还有枪弹 还有非常高的家伙
Guns. And obnoxiously tall people.
我怕死人 我呆不下去
And murder. I can't be here.
看到诸位已经做好战斗准备 挺好的
It's really cool, you guys seem ready to do battle and stuff, but...
不过说实话 我从没跟人动过手
Full transparency, I've never done battle.
以前都是推别人一下就跑
I just push some people and run away.
救一个
Save one.
什么
One?
先救一个人
Save one person.
哪个
Wait, which one?
别说话 别打架  进去 救一个人出来
Don't talk. Don't fight. Get in. Get one out.
然后呢
And then?
到时候你就明白了
You go.
好的
Okay.
真没用
Useless!
到你了
You then.
我的母盒在哪里
Where is my Mother Box?
我死也不会告诉你
I'll die before I tell you.
终于碰到一个有骨气的
At last, one that doesn't whine.
但我会让你尖叫的
But you will scream.
父亲
Dad.
维克多
Victor.
你是母盒孕育出来的
You were born of her.
一个混沌的产物
A creature of chaos.
对此 我不敢苟同
Not how I see it.
慢慢来
Give it time.
亚马逊族
Amazon!
好的
Okay.
救一个
Save one.
这个留给我
This one is mine.
你高估了你自己
You overestimate yourself.
孩子
Child...
我的斧头上还滴着你姐妹的血呢
My axe is still slick with the blood of your sisters.
阿尔弗雷德 我需要夜行者
Alfred, I need the Nightcrawler.
还以为你不需要呢
I thought you'd never ask.
夜行者已出发 正在启动遥控模式
Crawler's on the way. Initiating remote mode.
好了  你没事吧
You good?
大厅尽头有段楼梯
At the end of the hall there should be stairs.
好
Okay.
快走
Go!
他想得到再造引擎 他的母盒
He's after the change engine. His Mother Box.
- 你们必须阻止他 - 带他们到安全的地方
- You have to keep him from it. - Help people get to safety.
- 答应我 - 快走
- Promise me. - Go!
杀了她
Finish her!
抱歉 各位
Sorry guys,
我刚才没带武器
I didn't bring a sword.
天哪  他真高
Jesus. He is tall.
此画面致敬米开朗基罗的名画《创造亚当》
原来
So...
你是远古神的后代
You have the blood of the Old Gods in you.
他们早死了
The Old Gods died.
不
No!
注意
Heads up!
谢了阿福 后面交给我吧
Thanks, Alfred. But I'll take it from here.
我们认识吗
Do I know you?
原始的人类
Primitive beings.
我们上面是什么
What are we under right now?
是哥谭港
Gotham Harbor.
我们得走了
You all need to move.
- 你带他出去 - 戴安娜 来不及了
- You get him out... - Diana, there's no time.
我早已被恐惧淹没了
Also among my fears is drowning.
你在浪费我的时间
You are a distraction.
母亲在召唤
Mother is calling.
戴安娜  快来
Diana, come on!
快爬
Come on.
再造引擎
The change engine.
他就这样逃了
Did he just bail?
数百万美元的工程毁了 你真是威风不减当年
Millions in structural damage. You haven't lost your touch.
不过看到你多了几个朋友 我很欣慰
But it's good to see you playing well with others.
穿成蝙蝠的样子 我喜欢
Dressed like a bat? I dig it.
可能只是暂时的朋友罢了
It may be temporary.
那么
So...
是谁让你改变主意了
What made you change your mind?
荒原狼
Steppenwolf.
他夺走了亚特兰蒂斯族的母盒
He took the Mother Box from Atlantis.
他现在唯一需要的 就是人类之盒
All he needs now is the last box of man.
估计他现在已经搞到手了
If he doesn't already have it.
他没夺走
He doesn't have it.
我们要逃出去
We need to get away.
不  这里更安全
No. We are safer here.
食物吃完了怎么办
What happens when we run out of food?
有人会来的
Someone will come.
谁会来救我们啊
Who will come for us?
这里就像个洞穴一样
Wow. It's like a cave.
很像蝙蝠洞
Like a Batcave.
巴里
Barry!
我父亲叫它再造引擎
My father called it the change engine.
英国人在一战期间找到的
It was found by the British during World War I.
他们对其展开过研究
They studied it...
但当时甚至无法测算它的年代 它太古老了
but they couldn't even date it. It's so old.
于是将其搁置 直到超人去世的那天晚上
It was shelved, until the night Superman died.
它突然开始运行了
Then she lit up like Christmas.
他们把它带到星际实验室
They brought it to STAR Labs...
我父亲认出
where my father recognized it...
它是某种永久能量矩阵
as a perpetual energy matrix.
听起来好酷
That sounds cool.
我还以为它是个核弹呢
I thought it was like a nuclear bomb.
母盒一边毁灭一边创造
A Mother Box destroys as it creates.
它象征着一个生命的周期 只是循环的速度快了数百万倍
It's a cycle of life, but a million times faster.
我父亲认为可以通过它获取无尽的能源
My father thought it was the key to unlimited energy.
推导出新的公式 实现细胞再生
New formulas, cellular regeneration...
可它太难控制
But it's too volatile to control.
他用在你身上了
He used it on you.
我出了场事故
I was in an accident.
本来会死的
I should've died.
我父亲想 他可以用母盒
My father thought that he could use the Mother Box to
用神经机械增强并重建我的残躯
rebuild the broken parts of me with a few cybernetic enhancements.
没想到造出了一台活机器
Instead, he built a living machine.
这台机器比它的宿主更加强大
I may be stronger than its host.
太多了 能量过多
Too much. Too much life.
你脑袋里在想什么
What's on your weird mind?
肌肉 协调
Muscles. Coordination.
基本的细胞集成能力
Basic cellular integrity.
人类只能吸收这么多
A human being can only absorb so much.
母盒是用来重塑一颗星球的
The Mother Box was designed to reshape a planet.
所以呢
So?
有个人
So...
他比一颗星球更强大
What if you were stronger than a planet?
他的细胞在休眠 永远不会腐烂
Your cells lying dormant, but incapable of decay.
假设他身处电场内
If you were in a conductive field...
借用母盒的能量
A boost from the Mother Box...
可以让他起死回生
...could bring "him" back to life.
氪星飞船里有个羊膜舱
The Kryptonian ship has an amniotic chamber...
- 非常适合... - 不行
- Which would be a perfect... - No.
- 戴安娜  布鲁斯 不行
- Diana. - Bruce, no!
你根本不知道 你所面对的 是怎样的一种能量
You have no idea what kind of power you're dealing with.
哪怕只有一点机会
Even if there was a fraction of a chance...
那又如何 所以我们就要唤醒一个怪物吗?
That what? That we could raise a monster?
就像卢瑟当年那样?
Like Luthor did?
我们现在拥有的技术 卢瑟当时并没有
We have tech Luthor's never even seen...
超人已经死了
Superman is dead.
我们都很惋惜
We all wish he weren't.
我们不知道他目前处于什么状态
We don't know what state he's in.
但我们能把他复活
We know we can't bring him back.
这种科技水平 我们难以企及
But this is science beyond our limits.
科学的目的就是这个
And that's what science is for.
去做没人做过的事
To do what's never been done.
- 让生命更美好 - 也可能毁灭生命
- To make life better. - Or to end it.
科技就跟其他任何力量一样
Technology is like any other power...
没有理智 没有良知的话 会毁掉我们的
Without reason, without heart... It destroys us.
你是在冒险
You're risking lives.
拿大家的生命 甚至是无数人的性命冒险
Theirs and maybe countless more.
我们没有时间慢慢研究
We don't have time for a control group.
确实有风险 但这是必要的
Is it a risk? Yes. But it's necessary.
为什么冒险 因为你感到内疚?
Why? Because of your guilt?
布鲁斯 当时我在场 不是你害死了超人
Bruce, I was there. You didn't kill Superman.
有时候
At some point, even you...
你得学会往前看
have to learn to move on.
这是史蒂夫·特雷弗教你的吧
Did Steve Trevor tell you that?
超人曾经是全世界的希望之灯
Superman, was a beacon to the world.
而你呢
Why aren't you?
你能鼓舞人心 戴安娜
You're an inspiration, Diana.
不仅仅是救人而已
You don't just save people.
你让人们变得更好
You make them see their better selves.
可我一直没听说过你
And yet, I never heard of you...
直到卢瑟
Until Luthor lured you out
偷到了你男朋友的照片 这才把你引出来
by stealing a picture of your dead boyfriend.
你把自己封闭了一个世纪
You shut yourself down for a century.
所以别跟我谈什么向前看
So let's not talk about me moving on.
那个
You know...
如果她杀了你 我们不会报警的
That if she kills you, we'll cover for her.
我们还不够强大
We are not enough.
我们每个人都有所保留
Each of us in our own way has held back.
我敢说 荒原狼这家伙绝不会心慈手软 谈什么仁义道德
And I promise you, Steppenwolf is not out there talking about ethics.
他想毁掉整个世界
He's trying to burn down the world.
阻止他的办法
The way we're gonna stop him...
就是利用他自己的能量
...is by using his power.
用这个母盒的能量
This power,
来对付他
against him.
我同意
I agree.
我觉得让母盒重新合并这个主意 不太妙
I don't like the idea of reintegrating with the Mother Box...
刚才你出言不逊的时候我算过了
But I was running the numbers while you're being an asshole,
成功复活他的概率很高
and there's a high probability that we can bring him back.
好 但是复活他了之后 最好是能让大家开心
Right, but we mean bring him back, in like a...
"耶 他复活了"这种 而不是
"Yay! He's back!" way. Not in like a...
搞得像吓死人的
Like a Pet Sematary
惊悚片一样
scenario?
死亡的时候 总会失去一些东西 超人也在所难免
You lose something when you die. Even Superman.
也许不会失去理智 也许会丢掉灵魂
Maybe not his mind. Maybe his soul.
我会准备应急方案的
I'll have a contingency plan for that.
如果他醒来以后 第一眼看到的就是你
If he wakes up and you're the first thing he sees...
那你确实要准备应急方案了
You'll need one.
吵得真过瘾 接着吵啊
Well that was fun while it didn't last.
她本来能阻止我 我的激将法差点成功
She could've stopped me. I practically dared her to.
我不明白 你为什么要激她
I don't see why you're pushing her.
我们得增强信号
We'll have to boost the signal.
用蝙蝠车的扬声器放出来
Put it through the Batmobile's speakers.
你在转移话题
Now you're changing the subject.
- 我有个应急方案 - 什么
I have a contingency.
复活超人有风险 戴安娜说得对
Diana was right about the risk.
如果计划出了问题 我们就搬出大家伙来
If the plan goes south, we're gonna bring in the big guns.
但是
But that's not...
一般的大家伙可不顶用啊
Those are very big guns.
你现在有一个团队了
You got a team here.
在领导团队方面 超人比我更出色
Superman could bring this team together better than I ever could.
- 他的力量 - 领导力和你力量的强弱
- His strength... - It doesn't matter how strong you are.
和你具有怎样的超能力 毫无关系
Or what abilities you might have.
他比我更有人性
He was more human than I am.
他在世上生活过
He lived in this world.
谈过恋爱 参加过工作
Fell in love, had a job.
他不止是力量强大而已
In spite of all that power.
世界需要超人
The world needs Superman.
我们的团队需要克拉克
And the team needs Clark.
那他需要什么
And what does Clark need?
也许他已经安息了
Maybe he's at peace.
他会理解我们的
He'll get over it.
其实 我可以挖的超快的 只是..
You know, I can do this a lot faster. I just...
挖快了感觉有点不敬 这么想是不是有点奇怪
Is it weird that it feels disrespectful?
对
Yep.
你有没有感觉到
Do you feel a sense of confidence
我们在做一件极其错误
that we're not doing something horribly wrong
恐怖的事
and macabre here?
不觉得
Not really.
- 好吧  那你当时为何要回来 - 因为我亲眼见过荒原狼
- Okay then why are... - Because I saw Steppenwolf up close.
戴安娜告诉我的事
The stories Diana told us?
现在我信了
And I believe them.
我们会阻止他的
But we're gonna stop him.
我们的计划正是如此
That's the plan.
没错
That's the plan!
*好吧  我们还没熟 有点种族歧视
Okay, we're not ready for... Racially charged...
你当时是被闪电击中了吧
You got struck by lightning, huh?
对 简单来说 是那样的
Yeah... That's the abridged version.
- 那你.. - 遭遇了爆炸
- And you...? - Explosion.
醒来后 发现自己身处实验室
Woke up in a lab.
那我们都遭遇了意外
We're, we're the accidents.
对 没错
Yeah, that's us.
算了
Hey!
我们正在接近氪星飞船
We're approaching the Kryptonian ship.
预计三十秒后到达
ETA, 30 seconds.
我是为他来的
I'm here for him.
- 我发誓 我绝不会..  - 省省吧
- I swear, I would never... - Save it.
行了
- Okay. - Okay!
好的
Okay.
实在太惊人了
This is amazing.
太疯狂了
This is crazy.
怎么 现在才觉得疯狂?
What, now it's crazy?
你们几个疯子最好有点分寸
You lunatics better know what you're doing.
照片：超人养父乔纳森·肯特
卢瑟为了让他的怪物活过来 把电路都烧毁了
Lex Luthor fried the circuits bringing his creature to life.
要想唤醒母盒 这里的电能还不够
There's not enough charge to wake the Box.
我也许能办到
I might be able to do it.
我试试错电启动
I might be able to jumpstart it, I...
如果距离足够远
If I can get enough distance...
我能把很强的电流引过来
I can conduct a significant electrical current.
也许能唤醒母盒
I might be able to wake the Box,
如果 确定要这样的话
if that's still what we want?
先试试
We have to try.
这里应该是尽头了 所以
This must be the end of the line, so...
我就位了
I'm in position.
母盒准备就绪
The Mother Box is ready.
必须在母盒接触流体的一瞬间把电流导进去
You have to charge it the moment it touches the fluid.
五
- Five. - Five...
戴安娜说得对 这是个馊主意
Diana's right. This is a bad idea.
四
Four.
三
Three.
Three...
二
Two.
一
One.
时间紧迫 请求支援
Give us an ETA on all additional units...
他活了
He's back.
他不太对劲
He's not all right.
他在扫描我们
He's scanning us.
什么
What?
放松点  你的肾上腺素在飙升
Arthur, you need to relax. Your adrenaline's spiking.
因为他不太对劲
Because he's not all right.
糟了
Oh, no.
要不要鞠躬  还是直接跪下
Should we bow? Or show our bellies?
维克多
Victor...
停下
Victor, stop.
糟了  你在干什么
- Shit! - What are you doing?
维克多
Victor.
- 这是战衣的防御系统  - 住手
- It's my armor's defense system... - No.
自从见到他就增强了
It's stronger since the interface...
- 我控制不住 - 维克多 不要
- I can't control it. - Victor, no!
- 快关掉 - 想点开心的事 维克多
- Shut it off! - Think of happy thoughts, Victor!
卡尔艾尔  不要
Kal-El, no!
他不太清醒 不知道自己是谁
He's confused, he doesn't know who he is.
咱们这是掉进惊悚电影里了
Pet Sematary.
亚瑟 我们得把他控制住
Arthur, we need to restrain him.
让我来
I got him.
卡尔艾尔  氪星最后的子孙
Kal-El, the last son of Krypton...
记住你是谁
Remember who you are.
告诉我你是
Tell me who you...
克拉克
Clark...
我认识你
I know you.
别逼我动手
Please don't make me do this.
阿尔弗雷德 把终极武器搬出来
Alfred, I need the big gun...
- 是你干的 - 我也是不得已
- You did this... - I had to.
你不让我活
You won't let me live.
也不让我死
You won't let me die.
世界需要你
The world needs you.
世界需要你么?
But does it need you?
告诉我
Tell me...
《蝙蝠侠大战超人》中蝙蝠侠也曾这样问过超人
你会流血吗
Do you bleed?
克拉克
Clark.
求求你
Please...
住手吧
Please.
求求你
Please,
走吧
just go.
好么
Yeah?
我们走
Let's go. Yeah...
我的天 我流血了
Yeah. Something's definitely bleeding.
人类之盒
The Mother Box.
还是被他抢走了
He has the last one.
我们到这来了
You brought us here.
你想起来了
You remembered.
这是家
This is home.
你真好闻
You smell good.
以前不好闻吗
Did I not before?
别这样
Don't do that.
我们刚被痛扁了一顿
We just got our asses handed to us
荒原狼拿到了第三个母盒
and Steppenwolf has got the third Box.
那我们去找回来啊
So we find them.
只要母盒彼此靠近
If the Boxes are even close to each other
就会产生某种
there's going to be some kind
能量波动
of energy surge.
盒子肯定放在难以探测的地方
And Steppenwolf's gonna be keeping them somewhere where they don't read.
没有网络 没有卫星覆盖
No internet, no satellite coverage.
范围缩小了很多
That narrows it down.
还不够小
Not enough.
这就看 你到底是没本事找到
See, you can't find them...
还是你根本就不想找了
...or maybe you don't want to.
亚瑟
Arthur.
你倒是挺擅长把超人赶跑的
Yeah, that was a great way to get rid of Superman.
老兄 我不是故意那么做的
Man, I'm not doing this on purpose.
是啊 因为你控制不住机器
Right. Because you can't control the machine.
现在我说我血糖水平太低
Right, so is this a bad time
是不是有些不合时宜
to bring up my blood sugar?
我都饿扁了
Very hungry...
维克多
Victor...
你能找到母盒的
You can find the Boxes.
你与他们的能量是相通的
You share their energy.
我知道这挺难下手的 如果你晕过去
I know it's frightening. But if you go under...
我保证 我们会救你的
I promise, we will pull you back out.
别让那个人鱼打扰我工作就行
Just keep the Little Merman away from me while I work.
巴里 你去阿尔弗雷德那儿找点吃的
Barry, go find Alfred in the pantry.
回来之前 就上线
Then come back, get online.
大家互相核对一下进展
Everybody check everybody else's work.
听着
Listen,
你能不能帮个忙
just wanted if you could, put out a,
放条鱼去..那个..
if you were, an aquatic...
你懂的
You know...
你能指挥鱼吗
Do you, talk to fish?
水会听我的指挥
The water does the talking.
挺好的
Of course.
如果水流出现异常 我会知道的
If the current comes in strange, I'm gonna point the way.
好的
Okay.
慢着
Wait.
我来吧
Let me.
只是有点脱臼
Isn't this a little out of place.
克拉克的反应跟你预想的一样
So, Clark seemed to share your view on being woken up.
他差点杀了你
He could've killed you.
他回来了 我受点皮肉之苦还是值的
I was willing to make the trade.
还把露易丝带来了
And bringing in Lois Lane?
在机库里 你跟我说的关于良知的那些话 你还记得么
Remember what you told me about heart, in the hangar?
你肯定
I bet you...
以为我没听进去
...thought I wasn't listening.
谢谢
Thank you.
你心里清楚 你不能永远当蝙蝠侠的
You know you can't do this forever.
我现在干这行都很勉强
I can barely do it now.
荒原狼来犯
Steppenwolf...
阻止他是我的职责
This is the job.
是我的职责
It's my job.
一直以来 我都没有尽职
And I haven't been doing it.
只是被动应对而已
I've been reacting.
而不是主动出击
Not leading.
你说的关于史蒂夫的话
You know, what you said about Steve Trevor...
我不该多嘴 抱歉了
That wasn't my business. I'm sorry.
你用激将法 想让我领导大家
You were pushing me to lead the team.
但是如果决策失误的话 是会死人的
But leaders get people killed.
战斗时
I fought...
我从来
Always...
不会退缩
When I was needed.
但要说到带领团队 走到大家面前
But to lead, to step into the light...
告诉他们
And to say to people:
这值得你们去牺牲自己
"This is worth your life?"
要是搞砸了
When it's your fault...
大家就都没命了
They're all Steve Trevor.
只要撑过今晚
We make it through tonight...
以后你可以永远待在黑暗中
You can stay in the shadows forever.
打扮成蝙蝠的样子
Dressed up like a bat.
我不会告你侵权
I won't even sue.
前提是 我们能撑过今晚
If... we get through the night.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我们一起来到这里 可你却不进房子里待一会
You brought us here, but you've hardly spent a minute in the house.
我知道
I know... I...
我还需要缓缓
Just got out of a wooden box.
重新回到这个世界
What was it like...
感觉如何
Coming back?
很痒
Itchy.
我 说实话
I mean, honestly...
感觉很怪
Weird,
许多方面都怪
in so many ways.
- 但最主要的是 - 我不够坚强
- But, mostly just... - I wasn't strong.
我没能
I didn't...
你一定对我非常失望
You would've been very disappointed in me.
我没有
I wasn't...
我还是那个露易丝 尽职尽责的记者
Lois Lane, dedicated reporter. I...
我 真的
I just...
没关系
It's okay.
我之前离开你了 简直太蠢了
I'm the idiot who left.
但我回来了
But I'm back now...
我要让一切重回正轨
And I'm gonna make things right.
你把妈妈也叫来了?
You called mom?
当然了
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还以为 你会需要更长的时间
I was hoping it was gonna take you longer to...
恢复
...recover.
为什么
Why?
因为我现在必须送你走了
Because now, I have to send you away.
布鲁斯
Bruce.
他需要你
He needs you.
扭转世界的命运 所以
Fate of the world. I think that's the deal. He was...
他才那么着急
Pretty tense.
看来我确实欠他一命呢
Well, I guess I do owe him one.
是啊
Right.
这次不准死
But no dying.
独家新闻要留给我
And I get the exclusive.
我保证
Yes, ma'am.
- 真的是你么 - 是我 妈妈
- You're really you? - I'm really me, ma.
终于集齐了
At last.
统一之力万岁
Praise to the Unity.
合并吧
The three is one.
恐惧之母万岁
Praise to the Mother of Horrors.
荒原狼在那儿吗
Is Steppenwolf there?
抱歉
Sorry.
在波扎尔诺夫 俄罗斯北部
It's Porzenov. In Northern Russia.
是个核电站
The Nuclear Plant.
30年前出了场事故
Had a meltdown 30 years ago.
有些人想搬回去定居
There have been some attempts to resettle nearby...
不过那边看起来非常荒凉
...but it looks like really rough sledding.
谁愿意去这种地方住啊
Who picks this place to put down roots?
那些人也没别的地方能去了
People that are making it count everywhere else.
地球将从那里开始
The Earth starts changing...
发生变化
...it'll hit them first.
我们还有多少时间
How long have we got?
几个小时吧
A few hours.
普通的交通工具可没有那么快
Transport won't fly that fast.
交给我吧
It will for me.
统一之力让三个母盒精确同步
The Unity brings all three boxes together in perfect sync.
它的能量不断汇聚
Its power builds
直至溢出
until it can't be contained.
但如果我们能让每个盒子之间延迟一点
But if I can cause a delay between each box,
哪怕只延迟一纳秒
even for a nanosecond...
它的能量就会倾泻而出形成闭环
Its energy will cascade. Form a loop.
三个盒子之间互相侵蚀
And they'll feed on each other.
就这么简单? 直接把它们分开就行了?
And that's it? We just pull them apart?
没什么后果吗
No fuss, no muss?
分开母盒的时候还是会引发大规模的能量波动
Separating the boxes is still gonna cause a massive surge.
我必须在场
I have to be there.
你们得想办法撤离
But you guys should think about getting clear.
我们不会丢下你的
We're with you 'till it's done.
恐怕
Honestly...
还没到那个时候 我们就全死了
I think we're gonna be dead way before that.
说真的
And you know what?
我不介意 死的光荣就行
I don't mind. It's an honorable end.
但我们必须阻止荒原狼
But we've gotta shut Steppenwolf down.
超人不会来了
Superman's a no-show.
你没超能力
You've got no powers.
无意冒犯
No offense.
这家伙可能是内鬼 谁知道呢
This guy might be working for the enemy. We don't know.
你经常绊倒自己
You're tripping over your feet, and mine...
你真美
You're gorgeous.
很勇猛
And fierce...
很强壮
And strong. And...
我们的族人曾经亚马逊族打过仗
I know we went to war with the Amazons, but...
不过那时候我还没出生
but that was before my time.
说实话 我不想死
You know what? I don't wanna die.
我年轻 我还没活够呢
I'm young. There's shit that I wanna do.
我觉得
I just feel like...
我还没真正拥抱过海洋和陆地
I didn't really embrace the sea or the land.
我老是孤身一人
I've been a loner my whole life.
能做点这样的
But being part of something bigger,
大事
like this...
我害怕也许是因为
Maybe I'm scared because...
我注定
I'm meant to...
你的发言很精彩
I think that was beautiful.
你要是敢提这件事 我就把你喂鱼了
You say a word about this, and I'll meet every prawn I know.
他刚才说了什么 我一点儿都没听到
I honestly didn't hear anything after "We're all gonna die."
让他们来吧
Let them come.
我要拆了那座塔 突破防护罩
I'm gonna take out that tower and knock down that shield dome.
你们去阻止荒原狼
You get to Steppenwolf.
不用等我 完成任务即可
Don't wait for me. Just do the job.
阿尔弗雷德 准备开始广播
Alright, Alfred. Are we set to broadcast?
马上播放年度金曲
Playing all your favorite hits.
来啊 追我啊 臭虫子
Come on, follow me, you damn insects.
他们来了 他们全来了
They're coming. They're all coming.
我们似乎没有考虑到这个情况
We might not have thought this through.
他在吸引火力
He's clearing the field.
他撑不过三分钟的
He won't last three minutes.
那我们来好好利用这三分钟
Then let's use them.
听我指挥
On my lead.
他们飞走了
They're leaving.
爸爸
Papa.
走 跑到车里去
Everyone, get out!
他妈的
Son of a bitch.
计划不是这样的
This isn't the plan.
韦恩老爷
No, Master Wayne...
因为你们是战友
...this is the team.
嘿 要怪就怪女侠
Hey, blame the lady.
我们本来打算扔下你的
We would've left you
可她却喊我们回来救你
but she didn't ask for our vote.
看来你的妙计 就是送死?
So your genius move is dying?
你果然疯了
You really are out of your mind.
拿鱼叉打仗的人才是真的疯了
I'm not the one who brought a pitchfork.
- 你再飞一会儿  - 好兄弟
- Ride ain't over yet. - My man.
此画面致敬了乔尔乔·瓦萨里和费德里科·祖卡里所作的壁画《Seven Devils》
你所谓的征服
Is this what conquering is?
避而不战
Hiding from the fight?
开什么玩笑
Oh, no...
我会让你们倒在我脚下的
You're all mine.
- 多谢你送我过来  - 不用客气
- Thanks for the lift. - Yeah, no problem.
你能搞定吗
You got this?
这些玩意会不停的来袭
These things are gonna keep coming.
你负责技术 我负责杀虫
You get technical. I'm on bug duty.
好
Let's do it.
真棒 不过好恶心
Yes! That's gross.
谢谢
Thank you.
这不是...
This is not...
现在
Now,
你明白了吧
do you see it?
不知道你们那边具体是个什么东西
Whatever you're in the middle of...
那玩意正在飞速蔓延
It's spreading for miles.
卫星显示平民在往东撤离
Satellites show civilians moving east.
可能逃不出去了
They're not gonna make it.
巴里
Barry...
我需要你跑一趟
I need you to take a walk.
我的天 希望这是东边
God, I hope this is east.
戴安娜
Diana.
你不配碰
You're not worthy, to touch.
母亲
Mother.
她就是力量
She's power.
力量
And power,
就是唯一的法则
is the only law.
你们太弱小了 看不到真理
They're all too weak to see the truth.
是么
Well...
我相信真理
I believe in truth.
但我也坚定的站在正义的一方
But I'm also a big fan of justice.
漂亮
All right!
氪星人
Kryptonian.
需要我做什么
So. How do I help?
为他争取点时间
We buy him some time,
他应该能阻止母盒毁灭整个地球
he can stop that box from destroying all life on Earth.
我们是这么希望的
We hope.
好吧 我就知道你不是因为觉得我不错 才把我复活的
Well, I knew you didn't bring me back 'cause you like me.
我..没有..
I don't... not...
有平民
Civilians...
- 巴里已经去了 - 平民太多了
- Barry is headed... - There's too many of them.
这边肯定是东
Oh, yeah. This is definitely east.
动作真慢啊
Slowpoke.
我们来比比啊
Oh, it's on.
我去救右边的
I'll take the ones on the right.
没事的
It's okay.
抓紧 抓紧
Hold on. Hold on.
陀思妥耶夫斯基
Dostoyevski!
那个家伙还在闹腾么
Is this guy still bothering you?
超人
Superman!
我们得把母盒分开
We gotta pull these things apart.
再等几秒钟
A couple of more seconds...
你看准了
you'll see her opening.
会有冲击波么
Any blow-back?
会有很强的冲击
Big-time.
但我觉得 我们能撑住
But I think we can take it.
好的
Good...
因为我觉得 活着真是太好了
Because I really like being alive.
我也是
So do I.
克拉克
Clark.
我收回那句话
I take it back...
我想死
I wanna die.
老兄 我的脚趾好疼
Man, my toes hurt.
我都不知道脚趾疼的物理原理是什么
I don't even understand the physics of how my toes hurt.
一群小孩子啊
Children.
我这是一群小孩子并肩作战啊
I work with children.
你们有没有看到外面发生了什么
Have you guys seen what's going on outside?
我是世界的终结者
I am the end of worlds.
你们竟然
Who are you,
敢反抗我
to defy me?
地球本来
This world...
就是我的
...is my right!
你们绝对不会..
You will never...
不
No!
这不可能
This cannot be...
认得那个气味吗
Recognize that smell?
恐惧
Fear.
不 退下
No! Leave me!
给我滚开
Get off me!
这是命令
I command you!
不
No!
No...
我要杀了你们
I'll kill you!
把你们全杀了
I'll kill you all!
漂亮
Booyah!
幸好我没错过这个
Glad I didn't miss this.
同感
So am I.
对
Yeah.
现在她开心了
Now she's glad.
谢谢你 布鲁斯
Thank you, Bruce.
千言万语也无法表达我的谢意
Not enough for what you did.
我当时犯了个错
I did a mistake.
我只是想弥补而已
That's all.
你怎么把房子从银行赎回来的
How did you get the house back from the bank?
我把整个银行都买下来了
I bought the bank.
整个买下来了?
The whole bank?
把你的反射弧调成跟我同步的吧
Slow your reflex with me.
我已经老啦
I'm old.
怎么了
What?
爸爸 这个是
It's actually the,
犯罪实验室最糟糕的工作了
worst job you can get in a crime lab.
不过
But, uh...
我迈出了第一步
My foot's in the door.
有个朋友给我推荐的
Yeah. I got a recommendation from a friend.
这是份正经工作么
This is like a "job" job?
正经的
"Job" job.
真不错
Look at you go!
黑暗
Darkness.
真正的黑暗
The truest darkness...
并不只是光明消失了 那么简单
...is not the absence of light.
而是深信光明
It is the conviction that the light...
再不会回来
...will never return.
大概有一百 一百五十英尺
Must be 150 feet.
没错
Must be.
一张大圆桌
Big round table.
六把椅子
Six chairs.
摆在那儿
Right there.
不止六把
With room for more.
但光明总是会回来
But the light always returns...
指引我们 能让我们看到熟悉的
...to show us things familiar.
家园
Home.
家人
Family.
还有全新的
And things entirely new.
长期遭到忽视的事物
Or long overlooked.
让我们看到崭新的机会
It shows us new possibilities...
鼓励我们去追逐机会
And challenges us to pursue them.
对 杰瑞·摩娜斯科是主谋
Yeah. And Johnny Menasco runs the whole thing.
毕尔巴鄂那一单是他做的
I mean, he did the Bilbao job 2 years ago.
克罗伊登的货也是他的
As are all the storage in Croydon.
- 还有比利时的 - 对 还有比利时的
- The Belgian. - Right, yeah. The Belgian.
这一次 英雄们从黑暗中挺身而出
This time, the light shone on the heroes.
他们的光芒照亮了世人
Coming out of the shadows
我们再也不会无依无靠
to tell us we won't be alone again.
世间黑暗曾经太深
Our darkness was deep...
看似要吞没所有希望
...and seemed to swallow all hope.
但这些英雄一直都在
But these heroes were here the whole time.
提醒我们 希望尚存
To remind us that hope is real.
你能看到希望
That you can see it.
你只需要抬头
All you have to do is look...
看看天空
Up in the sky...
我的感激之情无以言表
I can't tell you how much I appreciate you doing this.
我不知道 巴里
I don't know, Barry.
我自己也很好奇
I'm curious myself.
而且这不是一场普通的比赛 你明白我的意思嘛
Yeah. And it's not like a competition, you know?
其实
Well, it...
这是一场比赛
It is a competition.
但这不是什么普通的健美比赛
But it's not like a macho- measuring thing.
如果我赢了 你就要离开队伍了
But if I win, you're off the team.
开玩笑的
No...
如果我赢了
If I win...
布鲁斯跟我说 你要带我去吃什么早午饭?
Bruce said something about you having to take us all to "brunch"...?
哇 说这种话 不能忍
Oh, see, now that's cold. That's a betrayal.
我觉得这太伤我心了
I feel stung by that.
好 要是我赢了 我会告诉大家的
Okay. But if I win, I get to tell everyone.
一言为定
Deal.
去哪个海岸
Which coast?
我从来没见过太平洋的全貌
You know, I've never seen the pacific.
就走那边吧 因为
Which is that way, because...
太阳在那个方向
The sun, and it's...
漫画中俩人也有过比赛 以平局告终
动作快点 卢瑟 跟我走
Come on, Luthor. Let's go.
卢瑟
Luthor!
好了 别耍我 卢瑟
All right, stop jerking around, Luthor,
要不然我就要进去把你拖出来了
or I'm gonna have to come in there.
他来了 欢迎登船
Ah! There he is. Welcome aboard.
钻石殿香槟：天价香槟 120万欧元一瓶
要不要来一杯钻石殿香槟酒
Care for a glass of Goût de Diamants?
我在庆祝超人重回人世
I was just celebrating God's return
又跑回天上去了呢
out of the ground and back up into the sky.
他和他的几位朋友们组成了一个什么联盟
He and his odd little friends are forming some sort of league.
你最好别再浪费我的时间了
You better not be wasting my time.
不 我活着 有很多重要的事要做
No. I have too much to live for and more important things to do.
威尔逊先生 我们要让竞争更加公平啊
We have to level the playing field, Mr. Wilson.
说白了就是
To put it plainly
我们是不是也应该组建自己的联盟呢
shouldn't we have a league of our own?